I can't see anything, after all, I don't want to see anything
It's a convenient world, isn't it? It's so painful, it's more painful than being in the water
I'm so tired of believing, that's how I've been doing it
Isn't this world strange? Why are you laughing? Why are you laughing?
Isn't it good to cry? I want to cry, but there's no one
What do you want in this world? Is it okay to live? Is it okay?
It's painful, it's painful, it's red, it's red, but it's so easy to be crushed by the rain
If you don't have a tomorrow, then that's okay
After all, nothing has changed, and my heart is about to break apart
Why is it so painful? What is not enough for me?
Can't you make it? All you can do is laugh
Who made this world?
I want to laugh, I want to cry
Isn't this world strange? Why are you laughing? Why are you laughing?
Why are you laughing? Isn't it good to cry? I want to cry, but there's no one
What do you want in this world? Is it okay to live? Is it okay?
I want to laugh, I want to cry
Isn't this world strange? Why are you laughing? Why are you laughing? Why are you laughing?
Why are you laughing?